In the next few videos, we're going to
be discussing Git and GitHub. And in
order to understand why you might need
them, I've arranged a little bit of a
demonstration. So, here
I have a very important, very, very
important list of numbers. Definitely
didn't just come from a Kaggle data set.
Um, but I need to update these. And at
the same time, my teammate also is going
to be updating some things. Um, he's
been asked to go down this column and
the black on red's a little hard to
read. So, he's gonna make the background
color a navy color and the the
foreground color, the font color, he's
going to make it white. So, really
important stuff. And I'm going to be
over here fixing these numbers cuz it's
actually been a month since this data
was collected. So, I need to go through
and collect the data. So, um, I'm going
to have my teammate get started.
And, okay, looks like he's started.
Let's see. So, this gu is going to be
25. This guy's 17. This guy's 23. Oh,
wait. No, that's supposed to be 22.
And oh, hang on.
Oh, that's supposed to be 17. 22.
25.
Uh, this is a nine. And oh, that wasn't
supposed to be nine. Supposed to be
seven.
And that's a 13. And some of you may
have noticed what is happening here.
When I hit control-z to undo some of my
changes on this month column, I actually
also undid some of my teammates changes.
So, wouldn't it be nice if my teammate
could make changes to this column on a
separate file and I could make changes
to this column and then we could just
put the two changes together. That would
be really nice. And that is the
principle that git is built